<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Coplanar Drawer Layout Example</string>

    <string name="this_is_a_header">This is a header</string>
    <string name="left_side_coplanar">Left Side Coplanar</string>
    <string name="right_side_coplanar">Right Side Coplanar</string>
    <string name="lorem_ipsum_bacon_text">Bacon ipsum dolor amet prosciutto salami venison, pork chop kielbasa shank ham hock drumstick short ribs porchetta. Cow chicken turkey landjaeger. Boudin pork loin pancetta filet mignon venison. Corned beef ham ribeye swine chuck kielbasa tenderloin venison boudin spare ribs shank. Pork loin fatback meatloaf swine spare ribs chicken doner tenderloin flank bresaola.

Alcatra pancetta bresaola tri-tip ribeye. Pork chop ball tip beef kielbasa bacon. Ground round t-bone picanha hamburger, turducken drumstick shank bresaola alcatra kielbasa bacon. Beef ribs spare ribs pastrami kielbasa andouille, pork jowl frankfurter t-bone ham drumstick. Rump kevin cow, fatback salami tail drumstick doner pork tri-tip shankle ham hock pork belly flank.

Tongue ball tip pastrami jowl porchetta doner sirloin biltong. Frankfurter pastrami beef salami, sirloin hamburger bresaola jerky shankle. Hamburger chuck flank, shankle frankfurter fatback strip steak. Chuck ham corned beef venison t-bone cow boudin, spare ribs kielbasa shankle landjaeger bresaola pork loin. Meatloaf shankle bresaola andouille meatball capicola pig pork sirloin cupim ball tip jowl ham hock. Rump chicken ball tip pork chop, beef tri-tip venison cupim kielbasa cow pig swine tenderloin.

Bresaola capicola short ribs kielbasa, boudin kevin short loin leberkas bacon cow tail ribeye landjaeger porchetta. Capicola andouille beef tongue tail. Drumstick venison shoulder tenderloin swine turkey pancetta. Ground round frankfurter beef ribs pancetta pig doner picanha. Rump strip steak turducken brisket biltong beef ribs, leberkas chicken shank sirloin short ribs landjaeger cupim.

Filet mignon landjaeger turducken jerky tail spare ribs t-bone sausage ball tip. Landjaeger flank pork pig biltong beef ribs swine. Kevin ribeye ham meatloaf biltong pork chop venison. Leberkas andouille kevin ham jerky, shankle picanha. Pastrami ham porchetta tongue tenderloin brisket, meatball rump pork loin pork belly.

</string>
</resources>
